limetray.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | LimeTray

## We collect but do not link personal and activity data.

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.  
We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.  
Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).  
We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.  
Our service does not currently recognize the "Do Not Track" signal that may be available in some web browsers. 

## We may collect but do not share your location history.

To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent on your first use of the service. 

## You can request to see or delete your personal data.

You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

## We may keep data indefinitely.

We may keep data indefinitely.

## We don't share your personal data with other companies.

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.

## No ad companies collect data through our service.

We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting.

## You can ask privacy questions.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:contactus@limetray.com

## Analytics providers access data on our behalf.

Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.  
Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.  

## We take detailed steps to protect personal information.

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.  
Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

Here is something to help you.   
Try reloding the page if it is still happening then let us know you can find contact details in footer.
